♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[squeals, in Visayan] Oh my God! This kid!
You're my daddy's maid, right?
- I'm an assistant.
- [quirky sting]
That's the same thing.
What's wrong with you?
[Tonet] AB positive?
So, that child has blue blood.
- Tatoy, your coffee.
- Ibyang.
[Janine] Daddy, I also know
how to make coffee.
It's tastier than what Ibyang made.
[retches]
[Atoy] Ugh! It tastes salty.
[Atoy] Ibyang, I want you
to make peace with Janine, okay?
I want you to apologize to her.
[Atoy] You? You can donate too.
You definitely can.
What's your type?
You.
[Janine] I'll try this on.
- [Ibyang] Hey! Don't go in there!
- [Janine mutters]
[Ibyang] We can't!
PREVIOUSLY
[Ibyang] Put that back.
[Janine] You're the troublemaker. What?!
[indistinct chatter]
[Denden] My phone!
[Emerson] You just walked straight, huh.
- [Emerson] That's it, that's it!
- Thank you.
- [Emerson grunts, groans]
- [Denden squeals]
- [Emerson gasps]
- [people clamor]
Wait. What are you doing outside?
Why are you here?
Ibyang sent me out.
[Atoy] I told her not to fight with you.
Where is she?
[Janine] She's in that… secret room.
You're not supposed to go in there.
Get out of here!
[Ibyang sobs]
[music fades]
[Ibyang sobbing]
[Tonet] What did you do to Ibyang?!
- [Ibyang sobs]
- Did you hurt Ibyang?
Why would I hurt her?
[Tonet] Then…
Then why are you putting ice on your hand?
What happened?
Ah, no.
I just got into trouble at the court.
There was…
Anyway, it's a long story.
But on my way home,
I saw… Ibyang outside, crying.
She wouldn't say why.
So, I brought her along.
Then I told Atoy that Ibyang was here,
so he wouldn't worry.
- [Ibyang sniffles]
- [Tonet sighs]
Come drink some water.
Stop crying now.
‪[gentle music playing]
Ibyang,
you know you can talk to Sis Tonet, right?
Why are you crying?
Tatoy got mad at me.
Uh, why? Did you do something wrong?
It was Janine's fault.
But I was the one scolded.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of you.
Of all things I dislike,
seeing you cry is the worst.
Because you know,
I love you so much.
[Tonet] Mmm?
Why are you crying?
This child is so frustrating.
You're making me cry too.
Don't cry anymore.
I'm not used to hearing
someone say they love me.
Only Sis Ame and Tatoy said that to me.
But it's one less now because of Janine.
[sniffs]
Atoy still loves you.
That won't change.
But he'll answer to me.
Just because he's my TTH
doesn't mean he'll escape my temper.
I love you too, Sis Tonet.
[suave theme music playing]
The manual is here.
If you want to change
the code of your smart lock.
All right, here it is.
Thanks.
Good thing you're available even at night.
This can't wait.
The kids got into that room twice already.
That can't happen.
There weren't kids here before.
Thank you.
You've helped me a lot more, Atoy.
This is a small thing.
If you have a problem, call me.
- I'll go ahead.
- Okay, bro.
- All right, bro.
- [Atoy] Okay.
[knocking on door]
[pensive music playing]
[tense stinging]
Oh, why?
Is there a problem?
[in Visayan] Yes.
You're not fair.
Huh?
[Tonet huffs]
Ibyang is at my brother's shop.
She's still crying.
[dramatic sting]
Of course. I scolded her!
I warned her. She didn't listen to me.
That's the thing!
She only obeyed what you wanted.
And she's still the one at fault?
Huh?
She just stopped your bratty daughter!
Hey, don't talk about
my daughter like that.
But it's true!
And now you're siding with Janine?
[pensive music playing]
Of course, I'm just doing
my responsibility as a father.
Father?
Father of who? Of your child?
What about Ibyang?
I feel bad for that child.
If you don't want her, say so!
Don't make her feel worthless!
Be fair, Atoy!
[dramatic sting]
[muffled chattering in the distance]
[Emerson clears throat]
- [Emerson] I'll leave you for now.
- Thanks, bro.
[Emerson] Mmm-mmm.
[Atoy clears throat]
‪[light tapping on table]
Sorry if I scolded you.
[Atoy inhales]
[Atoy] The truth is…
I was scared.
I was nervous for you.
What if something happened to you?
To both of you!
That's what I was thinking too.
That's why I stopped Janine.
But you got mad at me.
I didn't do anything wrong.
[Atoy sighs]
What I want is for you
to be more responsible.
Of course, you're the older sister.
[gentle music playing]
Older sister?
Yes, older sister.
We've been together longer, right?
So, for me, you're the eldest.
You're the older sister.
So that means
you should show her what's right.
She'll follow you,
and if she does something wrong,
if she doesn't listen to you,
if you see her doing something bad,
you are to tell me.
Can we do that?
[Atoy sighs]
Ibyang, we're one family now.
I'm the father,
and you and Janine are both my children.
But I want you to get along.
Well, it's normal for siblings to fight.
That's natural.
But who knows?
Maybe you'll even become best friends.
Right?
Mmm-hmm?
Let's go home, Tatoy.
I'll try again
for Janine and me to be sisters.
Very good. Come here!
Come here. Come, come.
[sentimental music playing]
Do you want dumplings?
Let's go.
Janine, you didn't tell me
the truth earlier.
Uh, was really
kicked out by Ibyang though.
[Atoy] Even so.
You still didn't tell me the reason.
Ibyang already forbade you,
but you still did it.
[inaudible] Tattletale, tattletale!
[Atoy] Psst, hey.
Enough of that, okay. Enough!
When I say enough, it's over.
I don't want that to happen again.
There's a reason
I forbid you from doing that.
It's for your own good.
Do you understand?
I don't want that to happen again.
- Is that clear?
- [inaudible]
[mellow music playing]
- [Atoy] Is it clear?
- Yes, Dad.
[in English] Yes.
All right then.
You both go to sleep now.
Tomorrow…
[clicks tongue] I'll take you both out!
- [pleasant music playing]
- [gasps]
Where are we going?
[Atoy] It's a secret.
Go, go to sleep now.
No more fighting, okay, Ibyang?
[Atoy] Okay?
[smooches]
Hey.
I'll have this bed for myself.
You sleep on the floor.
[pensive music playing]
[grunts] All right,
I'll sleep here instead.
Tatoy might get mad if we fight again.
Good night, Janine.
Why did you even come back?
You're not the real child.
[pensive music playing]
‪[dramatic stinging]
‪[dramatic sting]
Atoy? Ame? Ibyang?
- Boo!
- [Tonet squeals]
- [sneaky music playing]
- [Ame chuckles]
[in Visayan] This woman's
driving me crazy! [inhales]
[Tonet sighs]
Ame, I almost died from shock.
Oh, no. I don't want you to die!
You won't see it when Atoy
and I become a couple.
- I'm telling you.
- Oh.
What about your dreams?
Ah, they're higher than you, like this.
- [Ame] Hmm?
- Yes.
But with Atoy, yes, let's lower it a bit.
Here, yes.
Because it really seems… impossible.
Where are they? Where's Atoy, my love?
Where's Miss Cita?
Well, Miss Cita is at the court.
It's the second day
of the blood donation drive.
Atoy and the kids left early.
They said they'd go out.
Actually, I waited for you.
To give you this!
What's this? A bribe?
It's my thank you gift for you!
[bright music playing]
Because Ibyang told me
you defended her from Atoy last night.
And that you're one
of the people who love her.
It's nothing.
It means a lot to Ibyang.
Especially to me.
Because what if I'm suddenly gone?
You're exaggerating about that!
No one's going anywhere.
We're still far from that.
We're still far from
the end of the thread!
It's too early for a dramatic moment.
But Tonet, I'm grateful for our friendship
that's like a light switch.
[both, in English] On and off!
[both giggle]
[bright music playing]
Oh? What's this?
I thought it was too early for drama?
But Tonet…
I just want you to know…
[sobs]
I already know that!
That I'm your best friend
you never expected.
That you have a suit to deliver
to Quezon City,
to Sir Ralph Torres.
Atoy said you already know where it is.
- [sneaky music playing]
- Hmm?
- [Ame] Hurry up…
- [Tonet] Is this it?
- Looks like it, right?
- Best friend!
When you get back, we'll eat dumplings.
I'll go now, okay.
- Best friend, love you.
- Best friend!
- [Audrey] Tonet, hi!
- Oh!
- [Audrey] Um, I'll pick up
- Audrey!
Janine.
Is she awake?
[Tonet] Oh!
They left.
Atoy took the kids out.
Didn't he tell you?
Um, I didn't say I'd pick her up today.
Um, by the way,
how's…
Janine? Was there a problem?
Ah, none really.
I know my daughter has an attitude.
So, if she did something
or said something unpleasant,
I apologize on her behalf.
Honestly, her personality
is really different from you and Atoy.
She didn't grow up with us.
But even though she's like that,
Janine is my flesh and blood…
and I love my daughter very much.
[pensive music playing]
Uh… speaking of blood,
there's…
a donation drive at the court now.
While you're waiting for Atoy,
you can donate.
- [Audrey] Oh…
- [Tonet] Uh…
Don't be scared.
It doesn't hurt. Not at all.
And you'll help others too, right?
Who knows, someone might need
your blood type.
What's your blood type?
[in English] Um, O positive.
Just a common blood type.
[suspicious music playing]
[Tonet] AB positive?
So that child has royal blood.
No wonder she acts like…
a snooty princess.
[Siony] O positive!
You're the same as Atoy!
You're the same. That's good.
You can donate now.
See, we're the same,
Atoy and I.
But hers isn't common.
Uh, what did you say?
Ah, no!
[tense music playing]
I have to go. I'm in a hurry.
I need to attend to something.
- Okay, okay!
- [Audrey] Oh, all right.
[Audrey] Thanks, Tonet.
- Atoy doesn't want his things touched.
- [gasps]
[sneaky music playing]
Um… sorry. Ah, I was just curious.
Have a drink first.
It doesn't have poison in it.
Thank you.
Uh, do you know
what time they'll be back?
[quirky stinging]
I'll just call Atoy.
[line rings]
[phone ringing and vibrating]
[line ringing]
[Audrey] He really left his phone behind.
Actually, Atoy deliberately
left his phone.
So he could focus on the two kids
without work calls or other distractions.
[in English] Okay.
- There!
- What game is that, Daddy?
This is hopscotch.
We played this in the ‘90s…
when we were kids in the street.
So, you'll need a stone, okay?
Then you'll place the stone
inside the box.
Skip that one. You'll jump, step by step,
like… kangaroos.
Oh, get some stones, quick.
[light music playing]
Oh, Janine, follow me, okay.
[Ibyang] I'll do it!
All right, put it there.
Then, this first box, skip it.
Follow me, okay, oh.
Then two, one.
One, one.
[in English] Base!
Let's go back. Okay, go. Faster.
Two. Oh, oh, oh.
[chuckles] Easy, right?
[teenager] Brother, brother!
- Let me take a picture of you.
- Oh, sure.
[teenager] You look so cute
as father and child.
You even look alike.
Brother? Hello?
I'm his real daughter, not her.
Oh, is that so? I'm sorry. Okay.
[teenager] Here.
[in English] One, two, three.
There! Thank you.
Janine, did you really have to say that?
I was just telling the truth.
Oh, why does it feel like it's my fault?
[Atoy] Enough of that, okay.
Enough. Oh, Janine, your turn.
You go next.
Daddy, it's so hot here.
I feel like I'm going to melt.
Wow.
You act like you grew up with aircon.
[whimsical music playing]
Okay. Where-- Where do you want to go?
Anywhere cold!
I know, Daddy! Let's go there. Hurry!
Do you know… where they went?
Don't you trust Atoy?
If there's anyone who's the safest
to be with your child,
it's Atoy. Better than ten bodyguards.
[sneaky music playing]
I know that.
But I wish he brought his phone,
so I'd know what's happening
with my child, right?
[in English] Ms. Audrey, relax.
Let Atoy spend time with his kids.
Isn't this his time with Janine?
So, just give it to him.
[in English] You're right.
BE A HERO
DONATE BLOOD TODAY
What's the blood type again?
Ah, that?
I know the mother and father
are both O positive,
but their child is AB positive.
- Is that possible?
- Oh, no.
That's impossible.
[dramatic sting]
So…
So, Janine isn't Atoy's child?
[tense music playing]
Ah, miss, can you please explain to me?
Make it simple to understand.
Why it's not possible to have a child
whose blood type is AB
when the mother and father are both O.
Here's how it works, miss.
A child with blood type AB
must inherit one A allele
from one parent
and one B allele from the other.
Now, if both parents are type O,
they cannot pass on A or B.
Perfect explanation.
I just really needed to know,
because they might not believe me
that Janine isn't their child.
But miss, don't make the blood type
as the sole basis.
Because there can be human error
in blood group reporting.
Better yet, retest
the parents and the child
for accurate blood typing.
It's also best to do
paternity and maternity tests
for the child.
Audrey!
You're amazing-- Ouch.
You're amazing, miss.
That's right. Audrey.
Oh, is this okay now?
- Can I leave?
- [nurse] Ah, wait.
- [nurse] Just a moment.
- [Tonet] Ah, not yet? Sorry.
[in English] Sorry.
[rock music playing]
[Red] Thank you.
[mysterious music playing]
[Martina, in English] Hi, hon.
So, the maid just told me
Audrey brought Janine to Atoy's place
to spend the weekend there.
Did you know that?
Now I know. And?
[in English] Oh my God.
Hasn't your coffee kicked in yet?
Be nervous at least a little.
Why should I be nervous?
I'm not afraid of Atoy.
[in English] That's not what I mean.
Isn't it unsettling that Atoy
has been with Janine
for that long?
What if he notices
or finds out that the child isn't his?
You know, Audrey and Atoy are so excited
about their "child".
They'll only think Janine isn't theirs
if someone gives them the idea,
which won't happen.
Because only we know the truth, right?
[tense music playing]
[in English] Relax.
[Tonet pants]
[Tonet] Audrey!
[panting] Oh, Ame!
Why did you let Audrey leave?
[Ame] No, she decided to leave.
She even said she'd just
pick up Janine tomorrow.
So, where's Atoy now?
Ah, at the park.
I didn't tell Audrey where they were,
so she'd stop bothering Atoy.
Oh, then I'll deliver this later, okay.
Because right now, I need to talk to Atoy.
Wait.
[rousing music playing]
- [security] What do you need?
- I know Audrey Regalia.
[Tonet] I just want to talk to her.
It's important.
But, I'm-- I'm family. She's my niece,
so, she's also my concern.
Did Audrey have Janine DNA-tested?
[in English] Are you saying that Janine
is not really their child?
You've asked Tatoy for so much already!
He might go broke because of you!
Daddy can handle it.
He has a lot of money.
You're such a meddler, aren't you?
UP NEXT
- Meddler!
- [grunting]
- [man] I'll kill you, bro!
- [Emerson screaming]
[old woman] Twice…
[Emerson screams]
…escaped death.
On the third, it will be final.
If not you, then someone you love.
Send your men to follow that woman.
[Red] Don't let her get near Atoy.
If she resists, you know what to do.
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
[in English] Yes, boss.
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias